// data for baby chemist bonanza app

var chargeSymbols = 
    {'negative': '-', 'positive': '+'};

var questions = [
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'nitride', 'Symbol' :'N', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'N3-', 'Correct Answer' :'nitride', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'nitrogen', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'nitrate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'nitrite'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'phosphide', 'Symbol' :'P', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'P3-', 'Correct Answer' :'phosphide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'phosphorus', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'phosphate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'phosphite'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'oxide', 'Symbol' :'O', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'O2-', 'Correct Answer' :'oxide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'oxygen', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'oxalate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'peroxide'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'sulfide', 'Symbol' :'S', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'S2-', 'Correct Answer' :'sulfide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'sulfur', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'sulfate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'sulfite'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'selenide', 'Symbol' :'Se', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Se2-', 'Correct Answer' :'selenide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'selenium', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'sulfate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'sulfite'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'fluoride', 'Symbol' :'F', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'F1-', 'Correct Answer' :'fluoride', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'flourine', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'fluorine', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'fosphorus ion'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chloride', 'Symbol' :'Cl', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Cl1-', 'Correct Answer' :'chloride', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'chlorine', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'chlorite', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'chlorate'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'bromide', 'Symbol' :'Br', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Br1-', 'Correct Answer' :'bromide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'bromine', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'bromine ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'barium'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'iodide', 'Symbol' :'I', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'I1-', 'Correct Answer' :'iodide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'iodine', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'iodyne', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'iron (I)'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'hydrogen ion', 'Symbol' :'H', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'H1+', 'Correct Answer' :'hydrogen ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'hydride', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'hydroxide', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'hydronium'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'lithium ion', 'Symbol' :'Li', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Li1+', 'Correct Answer' :'lithium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'lead', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'lead (I)', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'lithium (I)'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'sodium ion', 'Symbol' :'Na', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Na1+', 'Correct Answer' :'sodium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'nitrogen ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'ammonium', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'nitrate'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'potassium ion', 'Symbol' :'K', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'K1+', 'Correct Answer' :'potassium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'phosphide', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'phosphorus ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'nickel (I)'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'rubidium ion', 'Symbol' :'Rb', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Rb1+', 'Correct Answer' :'rubidium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'rudibium ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'rabium ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'radon ion'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'silver ion', 'Symbol' :'Ag', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Ag1+', 'Correct Answer' :'silver ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'gold ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'lead (I)', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'agetate ion'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'magnesium ion', 'Symbol' :'Mg', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Mg2+', 'Correct Answer' :'magnesium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'manganese ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'permanganate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'manganate'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'calcium ion', 'Symbol' :'Ca', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Ca2+', 'Correct Answer' :'calcium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'carbide', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'carbonate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'calcite ion'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'strontium ion', 'Symbol' :'Sr', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Sr2+', 'Correct Answer' :'strontium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'sulfur ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'sodium ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'tin (II)'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'barium ion', 'Symbol' :'Ba', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Ba2+', 'Correct Answer' :'barium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'bromide', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'bromine ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'rubidium ion'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'zinc ion', 'Symbol' :'Zn', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Zn2+', 'Correct Answer' :'zinc ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'zirconium ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'zircon ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'zink ion'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'cadmium ion', 'Symbol' :'Cd', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Cd2+', 'Correct Answer' :'cadmium ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'caladium ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'canadam ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'calcium ion'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'aluminum ion', 'Symbol' :'Al', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Al3+', 'Correct Answer' :'aluminum ion', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'argon ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'ammonium', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'acetate'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'iron (II)', 'Symbol' :'Fe', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Fe2+', 'Correct Answer' :'iron (II)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'iron ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'iron-2', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'fluorine (II)'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'iron (III)', 'Symbol' :'Fe', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Fe3+', 'Correct Answer' :'iron (III)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'iron ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'iron-3', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'fluorine (III)'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'nickel (II)', 'Symbol' :'Ni', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Ni2+', 'Correct Answer' :'nickel (II)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'nickel-2', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'nickel ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'nitrogen (II)'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'nickel (III)', 'Symbol' :'Ni', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Ni3+', 'Correct Answer' :'nickel (III)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'nickel-3', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'nickel ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'nitrogen (III)'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'copper (I)', 'Symbol' :'Cu', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Cu1+', 'Correct Answer' :'copper (I)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'copper ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'calcium (I)', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'copper-1'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'copper (II)', 'Symbol' :'Cu', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Cu2+', 'Correct Answer' :'copper (II)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'copper ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'calcium (II)', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'copper-2'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'tin (II)', 'Symbol' :'Sn', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Sn2+', 'Correct Answer' :'tin (II)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'silicon (II)', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'tin ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'tin-2'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'tin (IV)', 'Symbol' :'Sn', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'4', 'Question' :'Sn4+', 'Correct Answer' :'tin (IV)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'silicon (II)', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'tin ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'tin-4'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'lead (II)', 'Symbol' :'Pb', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Pb2+', 'Correct Answer' :'lead (II)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'lead-2', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'phosphite', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'potassium (II)'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'lead (IV)', 'Symbol' :'Pb', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'4', 'Question' :'Pb4+', 'Correct Answer' :'lead (IV)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'lead-4', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'phosphate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'potassium (IV)'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'cobalt (II)', 'Symbol' :'Co', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Co2+', 'Correct Answer' :'cobalt (II)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'cobalt-2', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'cobalt ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'copper (II)'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'cobalt (III)', 'Symbol' :'Co', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Co3+', 'Correct Answer' :'cobalt (III)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'cobalt-3', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'cobalt ion', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'copper (III)'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Cation', 'Name' :'ammonium', 'Symbol' :'NH4', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'NH41+', 'Correct Answer' :'ammonium', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'nitrate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'nitrite', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'hydroxide'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'acetate', 'Symbol' :'C2H3O2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'C2H3O21-', 'Correct Answer' :'acetate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'carbonate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'oxalate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'hydroxide'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'cyanide', 'Symbol' :'CN', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'CN1-', 'Correct Answer' :'cyanide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'carbon ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'carbonate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'carbide'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'hydroxide', 'Symbol' :'OH', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'OH1-', 'Correct Answer' :'hydroxide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'hydronium', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'acetate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'bicarbonate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'hydrogen carbonate (or bicarbonate)', 'Symbol' :'HCO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'HCO31-', 'Correct Answer' :'hydrogen carbonate (or bicarbonate)', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'hydronium', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'carbonate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'carbonite'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'hypochlorite', 'Symbol' :'ClO', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'ClO1-', 'Correct Answer' :'hypochlorite', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'chlorate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'chlorite', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'perchlorate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chlorite', 'Symbol' :'ClO2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'ClO21-', 'Correct Answer' :'chlorite', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'hypochlorite', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'chlorate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'perchlorate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chlorate', 'Symbol' :'ClO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'ClO31-', 'Correct Answer' :'chlorate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'hypochlorite', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'chlorite', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'perchlorate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'perchlorate', 'Symbol' :'ClO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'ClO41-', 'Correct Answer' :'perchlorate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'hypochlorite', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'chlorite', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'chlorate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'nitrite', 'Symbol' :'NO2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'NO21-', 'Correct Answer' :'nitrite', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'nitrate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'nitride', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ammonium'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'nitrate', 'Symbol' :'NO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'NO31-', 'Correct Answer' :'nitrate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'nitrite', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'nitride', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ammonium'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'permanganate', 'Symbol' :'MnO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'MnO41-', 'Correct Answer' :'permanganate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'magnesium ion', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'macetate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ammonium'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'carbonate', 'Symbol' :'CO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'CO32-', 'Correct Answer' :'carbonate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'dichromate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'bicarbonate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'chromate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chromate', 'Symbol' :'CrO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'CrO42-', 'Correct Answer' :'chromate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'dichrmoate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'bicarbonate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'carbonate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'dichromate', 'Symbol' :'Cr2O7', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Cr2O72-', 'Correct Answer' :'dichromate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'chromate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'bicarbonate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'carbonate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'oxalate', 'Symbol' :'C2O4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'C2O42-', 'Correct Answer' :'oxalate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'carbonate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'bicarbonate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'hydroxide'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'peroxide', 'Symbol' :'O2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'O22-', 'Correct Answer' :'peroxide', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'oxide', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'oxalate', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'oxygen'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'sulfite', 'Symbol' :'SO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'SO32-', 'Correct Answer' :'sulfite', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'sulfate', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'sulfide', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'hyposulfite'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'sulfate', 'Symbol' :'SO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'SO42-', 'Correct Answer' :'sulfate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'sulfite', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'sulfide', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'persulfate'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'phosphate', 'Symbol' :'PO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'PO43-', 'Correct Answer' :'phosphate', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'phosphide', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'phosphite', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'peroxide'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'nitride', 'Symbol' :'N', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Nitride', 'Correct Answer' :'N3-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'P3-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'PO33-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'PO42-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'phosphide', 'Symbol' :'P', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Phosphide', 'Correct Answer' :'P3-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'P1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'PO43-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'P2-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'oxide', 'Symbol' :'O', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Oxide', 'Correct Answer' :'O2-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'O22-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'O1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'O3-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'sulfide', 'Symbol' :'S', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Sulfide', 'Correct Answer' :'S2-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'SO42-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'S1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'SO32-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'selenide', 'Symbol' :'Se', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Selenide', 'Correct Answer' :'Se2-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Se1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Se3-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Sl2-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'fluoride', 'Symbol' :'F', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Fluoride', 'Correct Answer' :'F1-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'F2', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'F2-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Fl1-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chloride', 'Symbol' :'Cl', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Chloride', 'Correct Answer' :'Cl1-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Cr1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'C1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ClO31-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'bromide', 'Symbol' :'Br', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Bromide', 'Correct Answer' :'Br1-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'BrO31-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Br2', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Br2-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Anions', 'Name' :'iodide', 'Symbol' :'I', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Iodide', 'Correct Answer' :'I1-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'I2', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'IO31-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'I2-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'hydrogen ion', 'Symbol' :'H', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Hydrogen ion', 'Correct Answer' :'H1+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'H1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'H2', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'OH1-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'lithium ion', 'Symbol' :'Li', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Lithium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Li1+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Li1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Li2+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Lt1+'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'sodium ion', 'Symbol' :'Na', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Sodium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Na1+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'S1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'N1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Nd1+'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'potassium ion', 'Symbol' :'K', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Potassium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'K1+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'P1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'P3+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'K1-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'rubidium ion', 'Symbol' :'Rb', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Rubidium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Rb1+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Rb1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Ru1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Rd1+'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'silver ion', 'Symbol' :'Ag', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Silver ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Ag1+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'S1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Si1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Ag1-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'magnesium ion', 'Symbol' :'Mg', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Magnesium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Mg2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Mg1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Mn2+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Mg2-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'calcium ion', 'Symbol' :'Ca', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Calcium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Ca2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Ca2-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'C2+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Cm2+'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'strontium ion', 'Symbol' :'Sr', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Strontium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Sr2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'St2+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Sr2-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'S2+'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'barium ion', 'Symbol' :'Ba', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Barium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Ba2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Br2+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Br1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Ba2-'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'zinc ion', 'Symbol' :'Zn', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Zinc ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Zn2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Z2+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Zn2-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Zc2+'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'cadmium ion', 'Symbol' :'Cd', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Cadmium ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Cd2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Cd2-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Cm2+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'C2+'},
{'ION Type' :'1', 'SubType' :'Monatomic Cation', 'Name' :'aluminum ion', 'Symbol' :'Al', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Aluminum ion', 'Correct Answer' :'Al3+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Am3+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Al2+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Al3-'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'iron (II)', 'Symbol' :'Fe', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Iron (II)', 'Correct Answer' :'Fe2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Fe22+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Fe2-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'2Fe1+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'iron (III)', 'Symbol' :'Fe', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Iron (III)', 'Correct Answer' :'Fe3+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Fe33+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Fe3-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'3Fe1+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'nickel (II)', 'Symbol' :'Ni', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Nickel (II)', 'Correct Answer' :'Ni2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'2Ni1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Ni2-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Ni22+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'nickel (III)', 'Symbol' :'Ni', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Nickel (III)', 'Correct Answer' :'Ni3+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'3Ni1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Ni3-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Ni33+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'copper (I)', 'Symbol' :'Cu', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Copper (I)', 'Correct Answer' :'Cu1+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Cu', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Cu1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Cr1+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'copper (II)', 'Symbol' :'Cu', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Copper (II)', 'Correct Answer' :'Cu2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'2Cu1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Cu2-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Cu22+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'tin (II)', 'Symbol' :'Sn', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Tin (II)', 'Correct Answer' :'Sn2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Sn2-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'2Sn1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Sn22+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'tin (IV)', 'Symbol' :'Sn', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'4', 'Question' :'Tin (IV)', 'Correct Answer' :'Sn4+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Sn4-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'4Sn1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Sn44+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'lead (II)', 'Symbol' :'Pb', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Lead (II)', 'Correct Answer' :'Pb2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Pb2-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'2Pb1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Pb22+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'lead (IV)', 'Symbol' :'Pb', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'4', 'Question' :'Lead (IV)', 'Correct Answer' :'Pb4+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Pb4-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'4Pb1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Pn44+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'cobalt (II)', 'Symbol' :'Co', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Cobalt (II)', 'Correct Answer' :'Co2+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Co2-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'2Co1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Co22+'},
{'ION Type' :'2', 'SubType' :'', 'Name' :'cobalt (III)', 'Symbol' :'Co', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Cobalt (III)', 'Correct Answer' :'Co3+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Co3-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'3Co1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'Co33+'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Cation', 'Name' :'ammonium', 'Symbol' :'NH4', 'Charge' :'positive', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Ammonium', 'Correct Answer' :'NH41+', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Am1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'NH31+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'NH41-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'acetate', 'Symbol' :'C2H3O2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Acetate', 'Correct Answer' :'C2H3O21-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'CH2O1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'C3H2O21-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'C6H12O61-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'cyanide', 'Symbol' :'CN', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Cyanide', 'Correct Answer' :'CN1-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Cn1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Cy1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'CN1+'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'hydroxide', 'Symbol' :'OH', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Hydroxide', 'Correct Answer' :'OH1-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'HO1+', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'OH1+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'HO21-1-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'hydrogen carbonate (or bicarbonate)', 'Symbol' :'HCO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Hydrogen Carbonate (or bicarbonate)', 'Correct Answer' :'HCO31-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'H2CO31-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'HCO32-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'HCO23-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'hypochlorite', 'Symbol' :'ClO', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Hypochlorite', 'Correct Answer' :'ClO1-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'ClO21-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'HClO1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ClO31-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chlorite', 'Symbol' :'ClO2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Chlorite', 'Correct Answer' :'ClO21-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'ClO1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'HClO1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ClO31-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chlorate', 'Symbol' :'ClO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Chlorate', 'Correct Answer' :'ClO31-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'ClO1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'ClO21-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ClO41-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'perchlorate', 'Symbol' :'ClO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Perchlorate', 'Correct Answer' :'ClO41-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'ClO1-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Cl2O21-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'ClO31-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'nitrite', 'Symbol' :'NO2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Nitrite', 'Correct Answer' :'NO21-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'NO31-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'N2O1-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'NO1-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'nitrate', 'Symbol' :'NO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Nitrate', 'Correct Answer' :'NO31-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'NO21-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'NO31+', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'NO1-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'permanganate', 'Symbol' :'MnO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'1', 'Question' :'Permanganate', 'Correct Answer' :'MnO41-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Mn2O72-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'MnO31-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'MnO1-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'carbonate', 'Symbol' :'CO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Carbonate', 'Correct Answer' :'CO32-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'CO23-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'CO31-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'CO42-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'chromate', 'Symbol' :'CrO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Chromate', 'Correct Answer' :'CrO42-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Cr2O42-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'CrO41-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'CrO32-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'dichromate', 'Symbol' :'Cr2O7', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Dichromate', 'Correct Answer' :'Cr2O72-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'Cr2O62-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'Cr2O42-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'CrO42-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'oxalate', 'Symbol' :'C2O4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Oxalate', 'Correct Answer' :'C2O42-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'C2O22-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'CO42-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'C2O32-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'peroxide', 'Symbol' :'O2', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Peroxide', 'Correct Answer' :'O22-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'O2-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'O21-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'CO42-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'sulfite', 'Symbol' :'SO3', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Sulfite', 'Correct Answer' :'SO32-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'SO31-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'SO42-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'SO22-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'sulfate', 'Symbol' :'SO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'2', 'Question' :'Sulfate', 'Correct Answer' :'SO42-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'SO41-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'SO22-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :'SO32-'},
{'ION Type' :'3', 'SubType' :'Polyatomic Anions', 'Name' :'phosphate', 'Symbol' :'PO4', 'Charge' :'negative', 'Strength' :'3', 'Question' :'Phosphate', 'Correct Answer' :'PO43-', 'Correct Answer Feedback' :'', 'Hint' :'', 'Wrong Answer 1' :'PO33-', 'Wrong Answer 2' :'PO42-', 'Wrong Answer 3' :''},    
];


var q;

for (var i=0; i<questions.length; i++) {
    q = questions[i];

    if (q.Name.toLowerCase() == q.Question.toLowerCase()) {
        // need to format answers
        q["Correct Answer"] = getFormattedIon(q["Correct Answer"]);
        q["Wrong Answer 1"] = getFormattedIon(q["Wrong Answer 1"]);
        q["Wrong Answer 2"] = getFormattedIon(q["Wrong Answer 2"]);
        q["Wrong Answer 3"] = getFormattedIon(q["Wrong Answer 3"]);
    } 
    else { 
        // format the question
        q.Question = getFormattedIon(q.Question);
    } 
    
    
    
    
    
}


// if it's a formula, need to format it for display
function getFormattedIon (strIon) {
    var formattedIon = "";
    
    for (var i=0; i< strIon.length - 2; i++) {
      if (!isNaN(parseFloat(strIon[i])) && isFinite(strIon[i])) {
        formattedIon += '<sub>' + strIon[i] + '</sub>';
      }
      else {
        formattedIon +=  strIon[i] ;
      }
     }
     
     //console.log('<sup>' + strIon[i] + strIon[i+1] + '</sup>');
    
     formattedIon += '<sup>' + strIon[i] + strIon[i+1] + '</sup>';
   
    return formattedIon;
  }



var oldquestions = [
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Nitride','Symbol' : 'N','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '3','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : 'wrong name 1','Wrong Name 2' : 'wrong name 2','Wrong Name 3' : 'wrong name 3'},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Phosphide','Symbol' : 'P','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '3','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Oxide','Symbol' : 'O','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Sulfide','Symbol' : 'S','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Selenide','Symbol' : 'Se','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Fluoride','Symbol' : 'F','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Chloride','Symbol' : 'Cl','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Bromide','Symbol' : 'Br','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Anions','Name' : 'Iodide','Symbol' : 'I','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Hydrogen ion','Symbol' : 'H','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Lithium ion','Symbol' : 'Li','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Sodium ion','Symbol' : 'Na','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Potassium ion','Symbol' : 'K','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Rubidium ion','Symbol' : 'Rb','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Silver ion','Symbol' : 'Ag','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Magnesium ion','Symbol' : 'Mg','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Calcium ion','Symbol' : 'Ca','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Strontium ion','Symbol' : 'Sr','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Barium ion','Symbol' : 'Ba','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Zinc ion','Symbol' : 'Zn','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Cadmium ion','Symbol' : 'Cd','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '1','SubType' : 'Monatomic Cation','Name' : 'Aluminum ion','Symbol' : 'Al','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '3','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Iron (II)','Symbol' : 'Fe','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Iron (III)','Symbol' : 'Fe','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '3','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Nickel (II)','Symbol' : 'Ni','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Nickel (III)','Symbol' : 'Ni','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '3','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Copper (I)','Symbol' : 'Cu','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Copper (II)','Symbol' : 'Cu','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Tin (II)','Symbol' : 'Sn','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Tin (IV)','Symbol' : 'Sn','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '4','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Lead (II)','Symbol' : 'Pb','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Lead (IV)','Symbol' : 'Pb','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '4','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Cobalt (II)','Symbol' : 'Co','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '2','SubType' : '','Name' : 'Cobalt (III)','Symbol' : 'Co','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '3','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Cation','Name' : 'Ammonium','Symbol' : 'NH4','Charge' : 'positive','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Acetate','Symbol' : 'C2H3O2','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Cyanide','Symbol' : 'CN','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Hydroxide','Symbol' : 'OH','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Hydrogen Carbonate (or bicarbonate)','Symbol' : 'HCO3','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Hypochlorite','Symbol' : 'ClO','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Chlorite','Symbol' : 'ClO2','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Chlorate','Symbol' : 'ClO3','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Perchlorate','Symbol' : 'ClO4','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Nitrite','Symbol' : 'NO2','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Nitrate','Symbol' : 'NO3','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Permanganate','Symbol' : 'MnO4','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '1','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Carbonate','Symbol' : 'CO3','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Chromate','Symbol' : 'CrO4','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Dichromate','Symbol' : 'Cr2O7','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Oxalate','Symbol' : 'C2O4','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Peroxide','Symbol' : 'O2','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Sulfite','Symbol' : 'SO3','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Sulfate','Symbol' : 'SO4','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '2','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''},
{'ION Type' : '3','SubType' : 'Polyatomic Anions','Name' : 'Phosphate','Symbol' : 'PO4','Charge' : 'negative','Strength' : '3','Correct Answer Feedback' : '','Hint' : '','Wrong Symbol 1' : '','Wrong Symbol 2' : '','Wrong Symbol 3' : '','Wrong Name 1' : '','Wrong Name 2' : '','Wrong Name 3' : ''}
 ]
 
 